Register of the Stephen E. Herbits Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Stephen E. Herbits papers,
1960-1993
75065
Hoover Institution Archives
71 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box, 1 envelope (31.1 linear feet)
Correspondence, writings, reports, memoranda, notes, and printed matter, relating to proposals for an all-volunteer armed force, Congressional action on the proposals, and evaluation of the new volunteer system in operation. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Herbits, Stephen E., 1942-
Access
Collection is open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1975.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1942 Born
1967-1968 Staff member, Wednesday Group, House of Representatives, United States Congress
1969-1970 Commissioner, President's Commission on All Volunteer Armed Force
1970 Project Leader, Open Presidency Task Force Study of Progress on Achieving an All Volunteer Force
1971-1972 Staff Assistant to Senator Robert T. Stafford, Vermont, United States Congress
1973- Special Assistant to the Assistant Secretary of Defense (Manpower and Reserve Affairs), United States Government
United States. Department of Defense.; Draft--United States.; Military service, Voluntary--United States.; United States--Armed Forces--Recruiting, enlistment, etc.; United States--Armed Forces.; United States--Military policy.
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1967-1974
  Scope and Contents note
  Letters arranged alphabetically by correspondent. Includes a few letters neither from nor to Stephen Herbits.
  - General (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Undated (Folder 2)
  - Allen, Dennis, 1972 (Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Martin, 1972 (Folder 4)
  - Bachman, Jerald G., 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Bakst, M. Charles, 1967 (Folder 6)
  - Beall, Thaddeus R., 1970-1971 (Folder 7)
  - Bentley, Judy, 1971 (Folder 8)
  - Blum, Albert A., 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Bunch, James C., 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Callard, David J., 1970 (Folder 11)
  - Clay, James, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Clymer, Adam, 1971 (Folder 13)
  - Dent, Frederick B., 1971 (Folder 14)
  - Dingell, John D., 1970 (Folder 15)
  - Downing, Thomas N., 1970 (Folder 16)
  - Flym, John G. S., 1971 (Folder 17)
  - Fortin, Joseph L., 1970 (Folder 18)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1971 (Folder 19)
  - Gallup, George, Jr., 1971 (Folder 20)
  - Gates, Thomas, 1969 (Folder 21)
  - Gerard, Robert J., 1973 (Folder 22)
  - Hamilton, Fletcher, 1971 (Folder 23)
  - Hechler, Ken, 1970 (Folder 24)
  - Heisler, Stanley D., 1973 (Folder 25)
  - Hilger, John R., 1968 (Folder 26)
  - Hull, Hadlai A., 1972 (Folder 27)
  - Johnson, Harold T., 1967 (Folder 28)
  - Johnson, James E., 1972 (Folder 29)
  - Johnston, Jerome, 1972 (Folder 30)
  - Jonas, Charles Raper, 1970 (Folder 31)
  - Kelley, Roger T., 1972-1973 (Folder 32)
  - Kilpatrick, James J., 1971 (Folder 33)
  - Koppelman, Charles, 1969 (Folder 34)
  - Krizer, Louis, 1972 (Folder 35)
  - Laird, Melvin R., 1972 (Folder 36)
  - Levin, Al, 1968 (Folder 37)
  - Lovenheim, David, 1967 (Folder 38)
  - McCulloch, J. Huston, 1969 (Folder 39)
  - McGee, Alexander, Jr., Mr. and Mrs., 1972 (Folder 40)
  - McWilliams, Carey, 1971 (Folder 41)
  - Marticelli, Joseph J., 1971 (Folder 42)
  - Martin, Richard, 1972 (Folder 43)
  - Meckling, William H., 1969 (Folder 44)
  - Michelson, A. A., 1967 (Folder 45)
  - Miller, James C., III, 1968 (Folder 46)
  - Montague, Robert M., Jr., 1971-1973 (Folder 47)
  - Moonan, Wendy, 1971 (Folder 48)
  - Moskin, J. Robert, 1971 (Folder 49)
  - Mudd, Roger, 1971 (Folder 50)
  - Nathan, Richard P., 1968 (Folder 51)
  - Nelson, Fred, 1972 (Folder 52)
  - Newlon, Daniel, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Oi, Walter Y., 1967 (Folder 2)
  - O'Konski, Chester T., 1969 (Folder 3)
  - Powell, James, 1969 (Folder 4)
  - Riper, Frank Van, 1971 (Folder 5)
  - Rogers, Bernard W., 1971 (Folder 6)
  - Rovere, Richard, 1971 (Folder 7)
  - Sandberg, Michael, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Schelling, Thomas C., 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Simons, Henry, 1971 (Folder 10)
  - Smith, Donald A., 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Snyder, E. K., 1972 (Folder 12)
  - Snyder, Jack, 1974 (Folder 13)
  - Spalding, Keith, 1968 (Folder 14)
  - Stafford, Robert T., 1967-1973 (Folder 15)
  - Steiger, William A., 1973 (Folder 16)
  - Steponkus, Bill, 1967 (Folder 17)
  - Stone, Dan, 1972 (Folder 18)
  - Swift, Pamela, 1971 (Folder 19)
  - The New Republic, 1971 (Folder 20)
  - Welch, Peter, 1971 (Folder 21)
  - Wool, Harold, 1967 (Folder 22)
  - Woosley, James, 1971 (Folder 23)
- OFFICE FILE, 1967-1993
  Biographical note, briefing notes, daily file, financial records, memoranda, notes, press release, printed matter, reading files, reports and schedule, relating to his office work and to the issue of organizing a union for the servicemen, arranged alphabetically by physical form. It also includes the work accomplished by the Commission on an All Volunteer Armed Force, of which Stephen Herbits was a member. See also DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE FILE and SUBJECT FILE.
  - Biographical note (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Briefing notes (Folder 25)
  - Daily file (Folder 26)
  - Financial records (Folder 27)
  - Memoranda
    - Undated (Folder 28)
    - 1967 August-November (Folder 29)
    - 1968 October (Folder 30)
    - 1969 August (Folder 31)
    - 1970 May (Folder 32)
    - 1971 January-December (Folder 33)
    - 1972
      - January-April (Folder 34)
      - May (Folder 35)
      - June-August (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
    - 1973
      - January-February (Folder 5)
      - May-June (Folder 6)
      - July-August (Folder 7)
      - September-October (Folder 8)
      - November-December (Folder 9)
    - 1974
      - January (Folder 10)
      - February-March (Folder 11)
  - Notes (Folder 12-13)
  - Notes (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Press release (Folder 4)
  - Printed matter (Folder 5)
  - Reading files. Includes charts, clippings, correspondence, memoranda, minutes of meetings, notes, remarks and statements (Folder 6-7)
    - 1969-1971
    - 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Reports
    - 1972 (Folder 4)
    - 1973
      - May (Folder 5)
      - September. Report was prepared by Stephen Herbits, John Johnston and Andy Uscher (Folder 6)
    - 1977 (Folder 7)
  - Schedule (Folder 8)
  - Subject file (Box 6)
    - Commission on an All Volunteer Armed Force
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Budget records (Folder 2)
      - Charts (Folder 3)
      - Comments (Folder 4)
      - Correspondence
        - Undated (Folder 5)
        - 1969 (Folder 6)
        - 1970 (Folder 7)
        - 1971 (Folder 8)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Folder 9)
        - 1969 (Folder 10)
        - 1970 (Folder 11)
        - 1971-1972 (Folder 12)
      - Minutes of meetings
        - Undated (Folder 13)
        - 1969
          - May-October (Folder 14)
          - November-December (Folder 15)
        - 1970 January (Folder 16)
      - Newsletters (Folder 17)
      - Notes (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Press conference (Folder 2)
      - Press release. It mentions Stephen Herbits as the youngest member of the Commission (Folder 3)
      - Printed matter (Folder 4)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Folder 5)
        - 1969 (Folder 6)
      - Reports
        - General (Folder 7)
        - Drafts
          - 1969 December (Folder 8-9)
          - 1970 (Folder 10)
        - Printed copy (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Statements (Folder 2)
      - Writing by others, 1969-1971 (Folder 3-5)
    - Unionization in the armed forces
      - General (Folder 6-8)
      - Correspondence (Folder 9)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Folder 10)
        - 1976 (Box 9)
          - February-April (Folder 1)
          - June (Folder 2)
          - July-December (Folder 3)
      - Printed matter (Folder 4)
      - Reports (Folder 5)
- DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE FILE, 1964-1974
  Budget, bulletins, charts and graphs, clippings, compensation and benefit records, correspondence, court proceedings, enlistment records, health records, housing records, interviews, memoranda, minutes of meetings, news briefings and press conferences, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press release, printed matter, programs, proposals, reading files, remarks, reports, schedule, statements, telegrams and television news reports, relating to the Department of Defense in general and the army, marine corps and navy in particular, arranged alphabetically by physical form. It also includes records dealing specifically with the questions of the draft, selective service system and with the publication of the book "How to End the Draft: The Case for an All Volunteer Army." See also OFFICE FILE and SUBJECT FILE.
  - General (Box 9)
    - General (Folder 6-8)
    - Budget records (Folder 9)
    - Charts (Folder 10)
    - Clippings (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Folder 12)
    - Memoranda (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Notes (Folder 2)
    - Printed matter (Folder 3)
    - Programs (Folder 4)
    - Reading files 1973-1974. Includes charts, clippings, correspondence, memoranda, minutes of meetings, notes, remarks and statements (Folder 5)
    - Reports
      - 1965-1974 (Folder 6)
      - 1975-1977 (Folder 7)
    - Subject file. Women in defense forces
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Charts (Folder 9)
      - Clippings (Folder 10)
      - Memoranda (Folder 11)
      - Minutes of meetings (Folder 12)
      - Newsletters (Folder 13)
      - Printed matter (Folder 14)
      - Reports (Folder 15)
      - Writings by others (Folder 16)
    - Writing by others (Folder 17)
  - Air Force (Box 11)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Budget records (Folder 2)
    - Charts (Folder 3)
    - Clippings (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Folder 5)
    - Enlistment records (Folder 6)
    - Housing records (Folder 7)
    - Memoranda (Folder 8)
    - Pamphlet (Folder 9)
    - Recruitment records (Folder 10)
    - Reports
      - 1968-1970 (Folder 11)
      - 1972 May (Folder 12)
      - 1974 February (Folder 13)
    - Telegrams (Folder 14)
    - Writing by others (Folder 15)
    - Miscellany (Folder 16)
  - Army
    - General (Folder 17-20)
    - Budget records (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
    - Bulletins (Folder 5)
    - Charts and graphs (Folder 6)
    - Clippings (Folder 7)
    - Clippings (Box 13, Folder 1-6)
    - Clippings (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Compensation and benefit records (Folder 2-4)
    - Contract (Folder 5)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Folder 6-7)
      - 1966 (Folder 8)
      - 1967 (Folder 9)
      - 1968 (Folder 10)
      - 1969 (Folder 11)
      - 1970 (Folder 12)
      - 1971 (Box 15)
        - January-February (Folder 1)
        - March-April (Folder 2)
        - May-July (Folder 3)
        - August-December (Folder 4)
      - 1972
        - January-July (Folder 5)
        - August-September (Folder 6)
        - October-December (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - 1973
        - January-April (Folder 2)
        - May-October (Folder 3)
      - 1974 January-June (Folder 4)
    - Court proceedings (Folder 5)
    - Enlistment, recruitment and retention records (Folder 6-7)
    - Enlistment, recruitment and retention records (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Handbook (Folder 2)
    - Health records (Folder 3)
    - Housing records (Folder 4)
    - Interviews (Folder 5)
    - Manual (Folder 6)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Folder 7)
      - 1966 (Folder 8)
      - 1967 (Folder 9)
      - 1968 (Folder 10)
      - 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 1970
        - January-June (Folder 2)
        - July-November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1971 (Box 19)
        - January-February (Folder 1)
        - March-April (Folder 2)
        - May-June (Folder 3)
        - July-December (Folder 4)
      - 1971-1972 (Folder 5)
      - 1972
        - January-March (Folder 6)
        - April-August (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - September-December (Folder 2)
      - 1973
        - January-May (Folder 3)
        - June-December (Folder 4)
      - 1974 (Folder 5)
    - Minutes of meeetings
      - Undated (Folder 6)
      - 1969-1970 (Folder 7)
      - 1971 (Box 21)
        - January-July (Folder 1)
        - August-November (Folder 2)
      - 1972-1973 (Folder 3)
      - 1974 (Folder 4)
    - News briefings and press conferences
      - Undated (Folder 5)
      - 1964-1971 (Folder 6)
      - 1972-1973 (Folder 7)
    - Newsletters (Folder 8)
    - Notes (Folder 9)
    - Notes (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
    - Pamphlets (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Poll records (Folder 2)
    - Press logs (Folder 3)
    - Press release
      - Undated (Folder 4)
      - 1965-1966 (Folder 5)
      - 1967-1969 (Folder 6)
      - 1970-1971 (Folder 7)
      - 1972-1973 (Folder 8)
    - Printed matter (Folder 9-11)
    - Printed matter (Box 24-32.)
    - Programs (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Proposals (Folder 3)
    - Reading files. Includes charts, clippings, correspondence, memoranda, minutes of meetings, notes, remarks and statements
      - General (Folder 4)
      - 1972
        - February-May (Folder 5)
        - June-August (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - September-October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - November-December (Folder 4)
      - 1973 (Box 35)
        - January-February (Folder 1)
        - March-April (Folder 2)
        - May (Folder 3)
        - May-June (Folder 4)
        - June-July (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - July-August (Folder 2)
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September-October (Folder 4-5)
        - November-December (Folder 6)
      - 1974 (Box 37)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February. Includes background information about Stephen E. Herbits (Folder 2)
        - January-February (Folder 3)
    - Remarks
      - Undated (Folder 4)
      - 1964 (Folder 5)
      - 1966 (Folder 6)
      - 1968 (Folder 7)
      - 1970 (Folder 8)
      - 1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - 1972 (Folder 2)
      - 1973 (Folder 3)
    - Reports
      - Undated (Folder 4)
      - 1957 (Folder 5)
      - 1960-1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - 1966 (Folder 2)
      - 1967 (Folder 3)
      - 1968 (Folder 4)
      - 1969 (Box 40)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - March-December (Folder 2)
      - 1970
        - February-May (Folder 3)
        - June-July (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - August-October (Folder 2)
        - November-December (Folder 3)
      - 1971 (Box 42)
        - January-February (Folder 1)
        - April-May (Folder 2)
        - June (Folder 3)
        - July-October (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
        - December (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
      - 1972
        - January (Folder 3)
        - February (Folder 4-6)
        - March (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2-3)
        - May (Folder 4)
        - June (Folder 5)
        - July (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3-4)
        - November (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - 1973
        - January-February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May-June (Folder 5)
        - September (Folder 6)
        - December (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - 1974
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
      - 1976 December (Folder 5)
      - 1977 September (Folder 6)
    - Schedule (Folder 7)
    - Statements
      - Undated (Folder 8)
      - Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - 1966 (Folder 2)
      - 1967-1970 (Folder 3)
      - 1971-1973 (Folder 4)
    - Subject file
      - Draft system
        - General (Folder 5-7)
        - General (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - Charts (Folder 2)
        - Memoranda (Folder 3)
        - Messages (Folder 4)
        - Minutes of meetings (Folder 5)
        - Newsletters (Folder 6)
        - Notes (Folder 7)
        - Pamphlets (Folder 8)
        - Press conferences (Folder 9)
        - Press release (Folder 10)
        - Printed matter (Folder 11)
        - Proposal (Folder 12)
        - Remarks (Folder 13)
        - Statements (Folder 14)
        - Surveys (Folder 15)
      - "How to end the draft: The Case for an All Volunteer Army". Stephen Herbits provided the authors, Congressmen Frank J. Horton, Richard S. Schweiker, Garner E. Shriver, Robert T. Stafford and Charles W. Whalen, Jr., with research and editorial assistance for writing this book (Box 51)
        - Correspondence
          - General (Folder 1)
          - National Press, Inc. (Folder 2)
        - Drafts. Typescripts (Folder 3-4)
        - Master copy (Folder 5)
        - Memoranda (Folder 6)
        - Notes (Folder 7-8)
        - Press release (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Printed copy (Folder 2)
        - Publicity file (Folder 3)
        - Reading files (Folder 4-5)
        - Statements (Folder 6)
      - Selective Service System
        - General (Folder 7-8)
        - Briefing notes (Folder 9)
        - Budget records (Folder 10)
        - Bulletins (Folder 11)
        - Correspondence
          - Undated (Folder 12)
          - 1966-1967 (Folder 13)
          - 1968-1971 (Folder 14)
          - 1972-1973 (Folder 15)
        - Executive order (Folder 16)
        - Memoranda (Box 53)
          - Undated (Folder 1)
          - 1966-1974 (Folder 2)
        - Messages (Folder 3)
        - Newsletters (Folder 4)
        - Pamphlets (Folder 5)
        - Press release (Folder 6)
        - Printed matter (Folder 7)
        - Programs (Folder 8)
        - Remarks (Folder 9)
        - Reports
          - Undated (Folder 10)
          - 1953-1959 (Folder 11)
          - 1966 (Folder 12)
          - 1967 (Folder 13)
          - 1970 (Folder 14)
        - Statements
          - Undated (Folder 15)
          - 1966-1968 (Folder 16)
        - Telegrams (Folder 17)
        - Writings by others (Folder 18)
    - Surveys (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams (Folder 2)
    - Television news reports (Folder 3)
    - Writing by others
      - Unidentified (Folder 4-5)
      - A-B (Folder 6)
      - C (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Ea-Ef (Folder 2)
      - F-J (Folder 3)
      - Ke (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Kr-L (Folder 2)
      - M-N (Folder 3)
      - O-Sta (Folder 4)
      - Ste-V (Folder 5)
      - W (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Miscellany (Folder 2-3)
  - Marine Corps
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Charts (Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Folder 7)
    - Memoranda (Folder 8)
    - Pamphlets (Folder 9)
    - Printed matter (Folder 10)
    - Reports (Folder 11)
  - Navy
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Charts (Folder 13)
    - Clippings (Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Folder 15)
    - Handbook (Folder 16)
    - Memoranda (Folder 17)
    - Minutes of meetings (Folder 18)
    - Notes (Folder 19)
    - Printed matter (Folder 20)
    - Programs (Folder 21)
    - Remarks (Folder 22)
    - Reports (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Statements (Folder 2)
    - Telegrams (Folder 3)
    - Writings by others (Folder 4)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1966-1974
  Bills and amendments, clippings, correspondence, hearings and testimonies, interviews, memoranda, newsletters, notes, press release, printed matter, remarks, reports, statements, status reports and miscellany, relating to the United States Congress and to the executive departments of the government, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - United States - Politics and government (Box 58)
    - Congress
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Bills and amendments (Folder 6)
      - Correspondence (Folder 7)
      - Hearings and testimonies
        - Undated (Folder 8)
        - 1966 (Folder 9)
        - 1971 (Folder 10)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Membership lists (Folder 2)
      - Memoranda (Folder 3)
      - Notes (Folder 4)
      - Press release (Folder 5)
      - Remarks (Folder 6)
      - Reports. One was prepared by Stephen Herbits (Folder 7)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Folder 8)
        - 1969-1970 (Folder 9)
        - 1971 (Folder 10)
        - 1972 (Folder 11)
        - 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - 1974 (Folder 2)
      - Status reports (Folder 3)
      - Voting records (Folder 4)
      - Miscellany (Folder 5)
    - Nixon administration
      - Elections
        - General (Folder 6)
        - Clippings (Folder 7)
        - Newsletters (Folder 8)
        - Notes (Folder 9)
        - Statements (Folder 10)
      - Domestic policy
        - General (Folder 11)
        - Clippings (Folder 12)
        - Correspondence (Folder 13)
        - Newsletters (Folder 14)
        - Printed matter (Folder 15)
        - Remarks (Folder 16)
        - Reports (Folder 17)
        - Miscellany (Folder 18)
      - Foreign policy
        - General (Folder 19)
        - Clippings (Folder 20)
        - Correspondence (Folder 21)
        - Interviews (Folder 22)
        - Memoranda (Folder 23)
        - Newsletter (Folder 24)
        - Printed matter (Folder 25)
        - Writings by others (Folder 26)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS, 1960-1976
  General note
  See also DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE FILE
  Charts, newsletters, printed matter relating to the Department of Defense, the army and the Congress arranged alphabetically by physical form. It also includes uncorrected advance proof of a book about the volunteer army. See also DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE FILE.
  - Charts, 1960-1972 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1967-1976 (Folder 2)
  - Printed matter, 1960-1971 (Folder 3-4)
  - Marmion, Harry A., "The Case Against a Volunteer Army", 1971. Uncorrected advance proof (Folder 5)
- Incremental material (Box 61-72)
- Declassified U.S. government records, 1970-1972 (Box 72)
  - 2011 September release of records, 1970-1972
    Memos, working papers, etc., primarily relating to the military draft, volunteer military service, and the military budget
  - 2018 release of declassified records, 1977 (Reading room workstation)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, undated
  - 1 print depicting Byron V. Pepitone, acting director, National Selective Service, undated (Envelope A)